Tomislay Diney

London, W13 0SA, United Kingdom 07539210185 • dinevtomislav@gmail.com

Personal Statement

I am applying for software related work in the IT sector since it has always been a passion for me, and it has always seemed to be the most interesting and intriguing profession that I can have. This profession has always pulled me into studying more and doing more compared to other jobs since it allows a look into the future of the world and how things would improve which seems very inspiring as it shows that there is always room for improvement. I like to get everything done as fast and as efficiently as possible which is why I think with the current and improving technology I am even more able to do so. I can even consider creating apps or new technology or at least helping with it so that ease of use and efficiency can reach new heights that were never seen before. I always had computer science as one of my main subjects as I chose it for GCSEs and managed to get a 7 which is one of my highest grades and then also took IT as my college course. I have managed to pick up skills in CSS, HTML, JavaScript, Python and C++ while doing my courses. I have done courses in Google Analytics and have also managed to do the IGD Work Experience week 2021 in both which I have gotten a certificate for my participation and success in completing both experiences. I have further done the Making the Leap training programme which has taught me employability skills like teamwork, leadership, communication etc. If I had to pick a language that I feel most proficient at that would definitely be Python. After successful completion of La Fosse Academy as a Tech Trainee I feel more confident in my skills and ready to embark on a journey in the IT industry.

Skills

- Critical Thinking
- Problem Solving
- Time Management
- Analytical Skills
- Teamwork
- Research
- Communication

Education Pearson BTEC

2020 - 2022

NQF BTEC NATIONAL EXTENDED DIPLOMA in INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY (MMM)

Drayton Manor High School

2016 - 2018 8 GCSEs:

- •Mathematics 7
- •Computer Science 7
- •English Language 5

Work Experience

La Fosse Academy | Tech Trainee | April 2023 – June 2023

•12-week intensive training covering key topics in the tech industry, including web development, architectural thinking and infrastructure.

• Completed team projects working to Agile principles.

IGD

06/2021 - 06/2021

Responsibilities & Achievements

I took part in the IGD Work Experience Programme that consisted of working with professionals in the specified categories:

- •Industry Insight Masterclass-Interesting Insight Information on what employers are looking for and how to improve in the future.
- •Marketing and Sales-Learned how to sell myself and my ideas so that they can grab attention.
- Engineering-Useful problem-solving skills and critical thinking.
- •IT & Digital-Quite informative as it made me more open minded into different parts of the sector.
- Employability Skills Masterclass-Became more aware of the importance of communication.

Training

Making the Leap ACE PROGRAMME- Training employability skills

Projects

Different projects I have been a part of can be viewed on my GitHub profile: https://github.com/dinevtomislav

Certificates

2022-2023

Range of certificates on different platform showing different skills.

Examples:

Computer Science Professional Certification - Codecademy

Diploma in Python Programming – Janets

Google Analytics for Power Users – Google

Further certificates are available upon request or can be viewed on LinkedIn profile: https://www.linkedin.com/in/tomislav-dinev/

References available upon request.